rehabs.com 2019-11-28

# Privacy Policy - Drug Rehab Options

This is a web site of Recovery Brands LLC.

Last Updated: April 27, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use and share information about you when you visit our Sites. By using the Sites, you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of information collected from you as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our Sites and not to information collected offline, including telephonically, via email, or through any other means.

## What Information Do We Collect From Visitors to Our Website?

Upon visiting our Sites, our server automatically logs your visit. The server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Additionally, we collect information you expressly provide. When using our site, subscribing to our newsletter, filling out a form, commenting on our blog or taking a certification quiz, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or other contact information. You may also be asked to provide information that will assist us in referring you or a loved one to an appropriate treatment center, such as information relating to the condition or ailment you wish to treat and your insurance information. Similarly, we may collect payment information, such as credit and debit card numbers, when you make purchases through the site.

We may monitor and/or record telephone conversations for our business purposes, such as quality assurance and training purposes and to protect our rights.

We may combine information we receive from you through our Sites with information about you that we receive from our affiliates and/or third parties. We will handle the combined information as described in this privacy policy to help us provide services and information to you.

## Do We Disclose Visitors’ Information to Third Parties?

We do not sell or trade to outside parties the information we collect from you other than as set forth herein. We may disclose information collected from and about you to select trusted treatment partners in order to match you with an appropriate treatment center. We may disclose the information we collect to third parties, including to our affiliates and business partners, who assist us in operating our Sites, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, respond to legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order), enforce our Sites’ policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information (including unique device identifiers) may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent for other purposes not listed here. We may disclose your personal information to a potential or actual acquirer, successor, or assignee as part of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

## How Do We Use Visitors’ Information?

We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:

  * To process a placement and/or consulting request
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our Website, address problems, and protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business (we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a promotion, survey or other Website feature
  * To communicate with you about information and updates pertaining to your placement and/or consulting request
  * To monitor the Site for compliance with our Terms of Use and the law

We may use non-personal information for statistical analysis, research, and other purposes.

## Cookies and Similar Technologies

We may use cookies to enable the site’s or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies and similar technologies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about Site usage and interaction so that we can offer better experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers that use these technologies to assist us in better understanding our Sites’ visitors. They may collect information about your online activities over time, on other devices, and on other websites or apps, if those websites and apps also use the same service provider.

We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Site and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners), and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

## Interest Based Advertising

We may partner with ad networks and other ad serving providers (“Advertising Providers”) who serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated sites. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information Advertising Providers collect about your visits to this site and elsewhere over time. Advertising Providers may utilize cookies and similar technologies to make advertising more relevant to you.

You may visit www.aboutads.info to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) self-regulatory program. Note that electing to opt-out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Sites, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Sites to their fullest potential.

## How Do Our Sites Handle Do-Not-Track Signals?

Some browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” (DNT) feature that, when activated, signals to websites and online services that you do not want to be tracked. However, there is not yet an accepted standard for how to respond to browser DNT signals, and we do not currently respond to them.

## Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California customers are entitled to request information relating to whether a business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this statute or who have questions more generally about our Notice and our privacy commitments to our customers should not hesitate to contact us at [privacy@recoverybrands.com](mailto:privacy@recoverybrands.com).

## Children

We do not direct the Website to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen.

## Email Policies

Recovery Brands will use reasonable means to protect the privacy of the information you send us by email. However, because of the risks outlined below, Recovery Brands cannot guarantee that email communications will be confidential. Additionally, Recovery Brands will not be liable in the event that you or anyone else inappropriately uses your email.

## Security

We maintain reasonable and appropriate measures designed to maintain information we collect in a secure manner. We have taken certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Website visitors. Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.

## Disclaimer Statement

All of the contents on the Sites, including any images, text, external links, graphics or any other material posted on the Sites, are intended solely for informational purposes. The information contained herein may be written by non-medical professionals and is not necessarily a substitute for professional medical advice, treatment or diagnosis of any disease or disability. Please seek advice consulting a qualified medical professional with any questions that you may have regarding your physical or mental health condition(s). If you are experiencing thoughts of suicide or any other medical emergency dial 911 or visit your local emergency room.

The Sites contain links to external websites and references to other resources that are not associated with our Sites. We have no control over these third-party resources and make no warranty or representation as to the content of those resources. Their inclusion does not constitute an endorsement or recommendation.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
Recovery Brands  
1200 Fourth Avenue  
San Diego, CA 92101  

## How Our Helpline Works

For those seeking addiction treatment for themselves or a loved one, the Rehabs.com helpline is a private and convenient solution.

**Calls to any general helpline (non-facility specific 1-8XX numbers) for your visit will be answered by American Addiction Centers (AAC).**

We are standing by 24/7 to discuss your treatment options. Our representatives work solely for AAC and will discuss whether an AAC facility may be an option for you.

Our helpline is offered at no cost to you and with no obligation to enter into treatment. Neither Rehabs.com nor AAC receives any commission or other fee that is dependent upon which treatment provider a visitor may ultimately choose.

For more information on AAC’s commitment to ethical marketing and treatment practices, or to learn more about how to select a treatment provider, visit our About AAC page.

If you wish to explore additional treatment options or connect with a specific rehab center, you can visit our homepage and browse by state, or visit [SAMHSA](http://www.samhsa.gov/treatment/index.aspx).

##  This Facility is Rehabs.com Verified. 

They are confirmed to be accredited, credentialed, and certified to provide the levels of care they claim to offer. Facilities cannot pay to be Rehabs.com Verified. 

More info at rehabs.com/faq/

Rehabs.com collects “Web Ratings” from dozens of popular sites around the web to help our users get a sense of a provider’s reputation and customer satisfaction. Our “Overall Rehabs.com Rating” and specific ratings on criteria such as Treatment Effectiveness, Meals and Nutrition, and others found on provider listing pages are collected from surveys taken directly by our visitors.
